[crowd cheering and applauding]
["Too Much" by Dove Cameron playing]
I'm Teagan Tao.
Those are my parents.
My dad owns boutique hotels, loves rowing.
Remember, stay within your pace,
keep it steady. You got this!
[Teagan] And my mom…
-Go, Teagan, whoo!
-[Teagan] …tries.
-Wow, it's really packed here.
-It's okay, I'm manifesting a spot.
-Of course you are.
-Look!
[Teagan] They're still madly in love.
It's gross.
To be a rower is to be all in.
Every 6 a.m. practice,
every punishing workout leads to this.
[horn blows]
♪ If you say I'm too much
Baby, go find less ♪
-Go, Teagan!
-Yes!
♪ If I'm such a big deal
Maybe you're too little ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, it's tough
I'm too, too, too much ♪
Come on, Teag!
♪ Baby, I ain't under pressure ♪
♪ Oh, oh, gather up, return to sender ♪
♪ Oh, oh, baby, I ain't under pressure ♪
[phone buzzing]
I have to take this.
-What?
-It's work.
Okay. Go, Teagan!
Hey. Hey.
I love you.
Okay. Oh, my…! Oh, my God, Teagan!
♪ …can't keep up, stay below, I guess ♪
♪ If I'm such a big deal
Maybe you're too little ♪
[Ella] Oh, my God, go, Teagan!
[Teagan] Your muscles are screaming,
but you push harder.
-Come on.
-You fight to get a split second ahead.
[Ella] Teagan! Whoo!
-[screaming]
-Yes, Teagan, yes! Oh, my God!
[announcer] The winner is Teagan Tao.
[phone dinging]
[sirens approaching]
[Ella] You did it!
[laughing]
[crowd clamoring]
[ominous music playing]
[Teagan] And when you finally get it…
Mrs. Tao, can you come with us?
Uh, don't touch me, please.
[agent] We have questions
about your husband.
[Teagan] …someone else's split-second
decision takes everything away.
[emotional music playing]
Turns out, my dad had
defrauded investors out of millions.
I need to see a warrant.
[Teagan] He disappeared
with my friends' parents' money,
while my mom and I were left with the FBI.
-[school bell ringing]
-Hey.
I lost all my friends.
They took all our money,
except for the education trust
that my dad set up.
My mom and I had to leave LA
and head back to her hometown.
My life as I knew it was over.
But little did I know,
my new life was just beginning.
["Triple Seven" by Wishy playing]
♪ A little bit uncertain
I wasn't really sure ♪
Eagle's Cove.
Is this where Dad's hiding out?
That's not funny.
Neither is ghosting your family
for six months.
Yeah, well, he's still your dad.
And we don't know the whole story, so…
[Teagan] Ah, yes. Denial.
The most annoying
of the coping strategies.
[Ella] It's not denial.
It's positivity. And it could be worse.
[Teagan] What's worse?
[Ella] I could be drowning you
with love and attention.
[Teagan] You're right. That is worse.
[laughing]
Are there any people here,
or is it all just…
-trees?
-[crow cawing]
Oh! There's the fudge store!
You don't like fudge.
No. Nobody actually likes fudge,
but I like that it exists.
Here's the Crab Shack.
I used to work there, you know.
They make the best crab cakes.
That's a heinous understanding
of what a cake is.
[Ella chuckles]
Does this new school
even have a rowing team?
Yeah. It's on their website.
They must suck,
because I don't see them
on any of the top ten rankings.
Easton Prep is at the top
of all the academic lists.
Do you remember Nanny and Grandpa's
from when you were younger?
[Teagan] From when I was four? Not really.
[Ella] You're gonna love it.
Hm.
[Ella] Here we are.
I always wanted to perform an exorcism.
Okay, yeah,
maybe it could use a little sprucing up.
-Is this, uh, Nana's stuff?
-[soft music playing]
[Ella] Yeah. I didn't have a chance
to pack everything up after the funeral.
[door closes]
[Teagan] No wonder they used to visit us.
Welcome home!
So it's not exactly like our old place,
but, uh, I think
we can really make a go of it.
This house might be growing fur.
Or it just… needs new curtains.
Okay, do you really wanna be here?
I mean, you love California as much as me.
We are in the middle of nowhere.
Oh come on, it's not that bad.
I mean, we're only
a half hour from Starbucks.
Mom, the coaches from Stanford
were scouting me.
I'm on a D1 scholarship track.
How are they gonna see me out here?
I know you're worried, okay?
-I know. But it's gonna be okay.
-How?
[sighs]
I'm gonna get some air.
I'll be back in an hour
if this… house stays up until then.
[Ella groans quietly]
[door closes]
["Care" by Hana Vu playing]
♪ I'm waking up to the sun ♪
♪ And I find it all too much ♪
♪ Oh, call this dawn, don't you know ♪
♪ I can't even talk about you ♪
♪ And I… ♪
[screams]
[Teagan] Hey!
Watch where you're going! What the…
-You're not gonna ask if I'm okay?
-You seem okay.
Are you going to apologize for hitting me?
You're zooming down the sidewalk,
okay? That's on you.
Your chain slipped.
Do you know how to fix it?
-Okay.
-Uh…
-What are you, um…
-Fixing your chain.
So do you live here?
Yes.
What do you do for fun?
We have clambakes, tubing, fudge.
If that's your thing.
All right, come here. See the drivetrain?
You gotta clean it
or your chain is just gonna keep slipping.
This thing?
This one…
should do it.
You didn't have to do that, but, uh…
thanks.
I'm Teagan. I just moved here.
Cam. Dillinger.
["Gospel" by Jean Dawson playing]
Okay, look, I gotta go.
Learn to fix your bike, okay?
Next time, I won't be around.
♪ Fall in love with a New York model ♪
♪ Take some drugs outside of Chicago ♪
You hit me!
[song ends]
There are four parts to a stroke.
The catch, the drive,
the finish, and the recovery.
Rowing, like life,
is a constant state of resetting yourself.
The most important part is the catch,
where your blade grabs the water.
It's what anchors you.
A bad catch can kill your run,
but a good catch will send you soaring.
[screams]
Okay, is this too much tweed
or not enough?
Button up and tuck the collar.
There's a little too much clavicle.
I never thought about my clavicle. Hey!
Why are you all dressed up?
I have a job interview.
This is the one, I can feel it.
[Teagan] Whoa. Can a building
have a British accent?
[Ella] I love the campus.
I always wanted to go here.
Not that they were admitting girls then.
[sighs] You're gonna love it.
[Teagan] Okay.
[Ella] Make friends.
Okay.
[Ella clears throat]
-Bye.
"Make friends"?
[elegant string music playing]
[Teagan] Okay.
[girl laughs] This happens every time.
[girls 2] It's so funny.
Where is she going?
[girl] Round and round and round and…
Hi! New girl!
Wow. What's your name?
I'm Teagan Tao.
Britney Garner. Student council president.
Yeah, I know what you must be thinking.
Garner, like Senator Garner.
Well, that's right.
Like mother, like daughter.
Vote for Garner 2044. [giggles]
I'll put that in my calendar.
-[Britney] Good.
-I'm Amber.
-Hey.
-I chair the dance committee.
It's a big deal. Welcome.
[laughs politely]
Look, I know the school's a whole vibe,
but you'll get used to it.
Everyone's pretty chill.
Ah. Nice to know it's not just yacht bros
and pretentious horse girls, you know.
[laughs]
[Teagan] No?
I'm the captain of the equestrian team.
-Which is great. And really impressive.
-Teagan! There you are! Yeah.
Come with me if you wanna live.
Britney. Amber.
Wow, that is the fastest
I've ever seen anyone
unalive their social standing.
How am I supposed to know
there would be horses?
What school doesn't have horses?
I'm your first-aid buddy, Juliet Morny.
-Hey. So is Britney, like…
-The most popular girl at school? Yeah.
She's smart, beautiful,
voted most likely to win
in a land war in Asia.
-That's terrifying.
-Ah, it's Easton Prep.
We're too well-heeled to be well-adjusted.
The prestigious school's
been around since 1798.
It's known as the Harvard of high schools.
Looks like the place where Swedish royalty
send their kids to lay low.
We don't have Swedish.
Prince of Spain goes here, though.
You wanna meet Federico?
No, that's fine.
That's the Sutton House dormitory, where
you'll find me and the other boarders.
You are a day student, right? A townie?
Parking lot's over there for commuters.
Unless you're coming in by helicopter.
It looks like a Skarsgård convention.
Who's the guy in the blazer?
That is Josh Regis.
Sixth-generation Easton Prep kid.
He was prom king when he was a freshman.
That's his cousin and sidekick Ryder.
He's made out with half the girls,
which isn't as many as it sounds.
This used to be an all-boys, right?
They only started admitting girls
two years ago.
Great if you're straight.
Less cheer for the queer.
-Yo, J, hook me up with that fresh meat.
-You are gross.
-Yo!
-That is Liam.
He made a fortune in crypto last year.
Looks like the summer break
did not crack the ego.
Avoid him. At all cost.
[school bell ringing]
We better get to class.
[Ella, softly] I was a client manager
for my husband's hotels,
and I think I can be an asset.
-Hi!
Ella?
Ella… Emerson?
I haven't been Emerson in a…
Wait a minute!
-Heather Wilson?
-Oh, my God!
I read all about you in New York Magazine.
Oh, my God, that article
was, like, ten years ago.
That photo of you lying by the pool.
Of course you'd be the one
to make it out of Eagle's Cove.
What are you doing back?
I'm shopping.
I need this.
[teacher] Hello, young poets.
We're going to be talking
about Byron's poem "She Walks in Beauty."
Byron was a snacc.
We'll read aloud
to get a feel for the language.
-Any takers?
-[Ryder laughing]
Mr. Regis, in case you didn't realize,
class starts at the bell.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Wu.
I would have been on time, except…
-I didn't want to be.
-[students laughing]
Do all the hot ones
turn out to be entitled assholes?
It's a flaw of evolution.
It's my bad. I didn't bring the book.
Will someone share with Josh?
Ah. Sweet! [clears throat]
Thanks.
[Josh clears throat]
She walks in beauty, like the night
-[soft music playing]
-Of cloudless climes and starry skies
And all that's best of dark and bright
Meet in her aspect and her eyes
[Wu] What do you think it means?
Miss Tao? Mr. Regis?
I think Byron was trying to smash.
Mr. Regis, if only you'd put in
as much effort into your English class
as your rowing,
you'd actually get somewhere.
Rowing?
Do you know where the boathouse is?
-[knocking]
-[man] Wanted to see me?
Coach Hayden. The Haverford Cup
is not far away. Are we ready?
It's too early to say.
There's a new crop from the junior boat.
Takes time to gel.
There's a legacy here, Coach Hayden,
which you upheld when you went here.
When I hired you, you promised
that you would get us back to the top.
-When's that gonna happen?
-It takes time to build.
We have very invested parents
who are contributing a lot
to the rowing program.
Mm-hmm. Contributing or interfering?
Yes, I'm very aware
of their generous donations.
But if the parents want success,
they're gonna need to back off.
Now I know what you're asking,
and it's non-negotiable.
He stays where he is.
But the same can't be guaranteed for you.
It's the last year of your contract.
I noticed.
I need results, Coach.
Yeah, good talk.
[quiet, intriguing music playing]
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
[Ryder] Is that pre-workout
still in the fridge?
-[boy] See what I'm saying?
-[Josh] All yours.
[woman] All right, boys,
drop your stuff quickly, please.
-It's erg time.
-Yes, ma'am.
[woman] Thank you.
-Hi, can I help you?
-Oh!
Sorry. [laughs] Uh, Um…
I was looking
for the schedule for the girls' team.
Are you Coach Hayden?
I'm Lana, the assistant coach.
Hayden's in a meeting.
We don't have a girls' team.
[exhales]
-Seriously? Are…
-Well, we wanted to.
But there weren't enough girls interested.
Or any.
We've only been coed for two years.
Well, there's interest now.
I am a lightweight sculler.
I'm really sorry, but one is not enough.
Can I at least train here?
Listen, you can't use the facilities
if you're not on the rowing team.
But there is a rowing club
a few towns over.
Membership's only 5,000 a year.
Good luck.
-Hi. How'd it go?
-Hi!
[Teagan groans]
[Ella] Oh, come on.
Don't do the teen thing.
Just actually tell me how it went.
Okay. Uh… Classes are fine,
and people are weird.
And there's no girls' crew.
That's disappointing.
Maybe you can find another sport?
[scoffs]
You really don't get it, do you?
What is this?
Mom? Are you hiding this?
-No!
-Mom!
-I was--
-$250?
-But I was gonna tell you. I--
-Take it back!
You can't put it on the credit card!
Hey, it's my credit card!
Argh!
["Keep Moving" by MØ playing]
♪ Uh, uh, uh ♪
♪ Gotta go far
Gotta be rich and be a rock star ♪
♪ Gotta have kids, get a big car ♪
♪ Follow your heart into the darkness ♪
♪ Go, you don't wanna blow
And this circus waits for no one ♪
♪ Don't ask, don't relax ♪
♪ "Am I gonna crash?"
No, you won't, just ♪
♪ Ahh! ♪
[song fades]
[exclaims]
["Circling" by Tiny Habits playing]
♪ Everything's circling around us ♪
♪ And promising a lifetime of love ♪
♪ However many times, it isn't enough ♪
♪ I love you, I love you, I love you ♪
[song ends]
Mm. Teagan, can I drive you in?
I thought we could talk.
Uh, I don't need a ride, thanks.
[school bell ringing]
Rowing's a bust.
What other sports do you have here?
Tennis.
Polo. Water polo.
[Teagan] I see.
Don't you have any real sports?
-Yeah. We have…
-[Teagan] Horses.
-Hey, new girl.
-Yes.
-Sounds fun.
-Did you get one of these?
No. What is that?
It's, uh, for girls
who are up for a little fun.
Are you fun?
New girl.
Me?
No, and never with you.
Hi! Hi, babe.
Hey.
Excuse me.
He's dating Britney.
Since freshman year,
Easton's power couple.
I can't tell if I'd do both or neither.
How can someone be so compelling
and repulsive at the same time?
[Juliet] It's a betrayal of the loins.
Do not make an enemy of those two.
Making enemies with beautiful people,
such a waste.
Ah! The Town.
They throw a big party
down at the waterfront every year.
Are you going?
I prefer my nights without keg stands,
but hey, I'd consider. You?
[woman on PA] Teagan Tao. Report to
the Head of School's Office immediately.
-Ooh, someone's in trouble.
-[tense music playing]
[Cabrera] Breaking and entering are not
becoming of an Easton Prep student.
To be fair, it was mostly just entering
and very minimal breaking.
Hardly the point.
You know how dangerous it is
to go out on the water by yourself.
-I'll be calling your mother.
-[exhales]
-Am I getting expelled?
-No. No.
But you're gonna wish you were.
Hey, dock wench. You missed a spot.
I heard you were into crew.
Why don't I take you out tonight?
You can show me your stroke.
Mm, I can't. I have plans
to vomit profusely at that idea.
You always had a way with ladies, Liam.
Don't talk to me, Faid.
-Hi.
-You good?
So you go to Easton.
Yeah.
-And you're a rower.
-Yeah.
What's a faid?
It's short for "financial aid."
I'm a scholarship kid.
They love to remind me of it.
That's not okay.
It is what it is.
So this is rowing.
I see why you come.
-[Liam] Okay. Places. Here we go.
-[Teagan] Interesting seat assignments.
Here's the deal.
Every seat in the boat has a job,
but the seat that matters most
is the stroke seat.
Otherwise known as "eight seat,"
where you put your best rower.
Or in this case, Josh.
Next, in seven seat.
So close to stroke and yet so far away.
Then comes the engine room.
The six, five, four, and three.
-Those are the powerhouses.
-[Liam] Where's your cable?
Then there's bow pair, and they…
-um…
-[Liam] Is this hard?
…have good technique.
The weaklings.
Why does Liam get a free ride?
-[Teagan] He's the cox.
-Excuse me?
[laughing] Short for coxswain.
It's the name of the position.
[suggestively] Oh.
We're gonna have to move past this.
[Liam] Know how hard it is to do this job
when you guys can't get together?
Follow the stroke's pace!
-Yo, we're on Josh!
-[energetic music playing]
You're already tired!
Drive! Drive!
Legs! Legs! Legs! Legs! Josh!
[Lana] Time.
I swear… Again!
[Lian] Josh! Your puddles are shit.
-Yeah, yeah, man. I got it.
-[Liam] Do something! Do you?
This is basic stuff.
-Did they get worse?
-I'm telling you.
I can't believe this. Again!
-You're literally jelly legs, bro.
-Just piss off.
[oarlock rattling]
-[rower] Whoa!
-[Liam] Oh, my God!
[rower 2] What the fuck?
I'm good. Sorry. My bad.
-Ugh.
-Ouch.
That's what you call catching a crab.
And that will kill your run.
And now the debrief.
-Less sweating, more strategy.
-[Liam] And up.
[Juliet] Is there going to be crying?
-[Liam] Down.
-[Teagan] Probably not.
[Juliet] Boring.
[Liam] Walk it out.
I'm out.
-Bye.
-Mm.
-[Liam] Yo, Crabcatcher! What was that?
-[Josh] Your calls are no good either.
[Liam] Yeah, says the guy
who can't get the stroke rate up.
[Lana] Well, that could have gone better.
[Hayden] I'm thinking we drop Ryder,
pull up Cam.
Ryder's not the problem, though.
Excuse me?
Don't drop Ryder down. It's unfair.
He's not rowing well
because he's trying to match Josh.
Josh wasn't pulling enough.
Look at his puddles, you should…
swap him.
All right.
Who would you put on the throne?
Cam has the best technique
and he's working the hardest,
but, uh, the team's not a fan of his.
So, it's the big guy in six.
-Bronson.
-Baloo.
Yeah. Dunno if he has the brains,
but he's got the brawn,
and he's got the team's love,
which you need
because your coxie's lost the team.
Astute.
-What do you think? You wanna switch Josh?
-Who, me?
-Yeah.
-I would like to keep my job. Thank you.
I won't have one to worry about soon
if we don't start winning, no?
Boys. Back in the water.
Last setup of the day,
but we're gonna change it up.
Baloo, you're in eight. Ryder, seven.
Cam, six. Josh, bow.
[tense music playing]
Holy shit!
-What the hell?
-We're trying something out.
-Coach, you can't do this.
-[Hayden] Get in the boat.
You can't do this.
Get in the boat.
[tense music continues]
All right, let's go, ladies.
[Liam] All right, everybody ready?
-[rower] Yes, sir.
-[Liam] All right, listen up. And row.
Come on, boys. Let's go, let's go!
Come on. Let's go. Whoo!
[Liam] You want it? You got your shot.
[stopwatch beeping]
Shaved eight seconds.
Give me some. Give me some.
Give me some. Let's go, bro!
-See that shit? Whoo!
-[Cam] Come on, Baloo.
Hey! You.
What is your problem?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I saw you talking to the coach.
I've been in stroke seat since I've been
at this school. Suddenly I'm down to bow?
Maybe you're not the best rower.
Maybe you're not pulling your weight.
Maybe you should keep your head
in the boat instead of up your ass.
[laughs]
-Who do you think you are?
-Who the hell are you?
Oh.
Oh, I'm Josh Regis.
Watch yourself.
[Teagan laughs]
[snaps]
["300 Dreams" by After playing]
♪ Oh, look at the state of me ♪
[object snaps]
[Teagan sighs] No…
♪ …falling down ♪
♪ Oh, look at the state of me ♪
♪ I'm always falling down ♪
-Hey.
-[Cam] Ever think biking's not your thing?
Tire's toast.
-I heard Josh ream you out.
-Mm.
Or you reamed him out.
Not my smartest move.
Easton Prep is a hard crowd.
They'll do everything they can
to make you feel like you're less.
You're not.
Don't back down.
Everyone's going
to the dock party tonight.
-I heard.
-But you should go.
There's more to the Cove
than the Easton snobs.
I'll, uh, think about it.
I'm… I have an extra wristband.
Text me if you want it.
Maybe I'll see you later.
Let's get your bike.
[soft music playing]
Oh… This is a knockoff.
Ah! For drag.
Or for burning. Nothing in between.
-Juliet, I don't need a donate pile.
-[laughs] It's adorable you think so.
You're not working a club girl working
bottle service on the Sunset Strip.
-Hey, that's cute.
-It reeks of effort.
And the one unwritten rule of Easton Prep
is never look like you're trying.
[Teagan] Can't I a little?
[Siri] You have one notification.
Message from Kesha.
-Would you like to open it?
-Ignore.
-Sorry… what?
-[Juliet] It's not what you think.
When my parents have bad news,
they share it by celebrity messenger.
They think it'll soften the blow.
Juliet, that's amazing.
Until Zendaya tells you
your grandmother's passed away.
Please open it.
Only if you try this on.
[Juliet] Mm-hmm.
-I don't know.
-You can trust me.
I don't know. Isn't it a little short?
[over recording] Hey, Juliet,
it's your girl Kesha.
I heard from your mom
that it is your birthday.
So happy birthday, bitch.
We all know
it's not a party until I walk in.
And your parents wanted me to let you know
that I'm not going to be walking in,
and neither are they.
Bummer. I kno--
-Harsh.
-Happy birthday?
They love that I'm 3,500 miles away.
I'm easier to forget.
But enough melodrama.
We need a hair curler.
I think it's in one of the boxes.
Maybe it's in my mom's room.
One sec.
[intriguing music playing]
What the hell?
It's my dad's stuff.
She was hiding it in her hamper.
-Dad's not in the picture?
-No, I… I don't know why she has it.
Uh… Hey, do you think
we can finish changing in your dorm?
Of course.
Okay.
All families are weird.
-[sighs]
-[footsteps approaching]
[Ella] Hey. Where are you going?
Out.
[Ella] I-is everything okay?
[exhales] No.
[melancholy music playing]
-[seagull calling]
-[distant ship horn blaring]
[man] Yeah, so I told them,
"You're being shellfish!"
-[man 2] Yeah, that's really good.
-[woman] Amazing.
[woman 2] All right,
they better have a good crab salad.
Jim.
-[laughs]
-Ella!
[Jim] Hang on. [laughs]
Uh, table nine.
[both laughing]
Well, if it isn't Miss Eagle's Cove 2003.
Ella Emerson, how the heck are you?
I'm broke.
I have no idea where my husband is.
I sold everything I had
to buy a car to get out of town.
And my daughter hates me.
I messed up.
Come on. You gotta buck up. Life goes on.
You always hated David.
-And you were right.
-I liked the other guy better.
Eh… I'll pour another.
Oh, sorry, get back to work.
You're in the weeds.
We've been short ever since Jane retired.
I don't know how many more
of these shifts I can take.
You want me to go back there?
-Don't play me.
-No, Jim. I-I… I need a job.
Can I come back?
You close tonight.
["Truth of Pursuit"
by Sarah Kinsley playing]
-[tires screech]
-[engine roars]
♪ …baby, you were mine ♪
♪ I think about it
Almost every night on the line ♪
♪ Do you ever wonder
How our stars will align? ♪
[Juliet laughs]
[Teagan squeals, laughs excitedly]
Wow.
Well, if my mom grounds me,
I hope the party's worth it.
[Juliet] She cares enough to ground you.
More than some of us get.
[Teagan] You don't get grounded?
You're not trying hard enough.
[Juliet] That would mean they'd have to
take a minute away from their own lives.
Count your blessings.
♪ Oh, I wanna feel alive ♪
♪ Like I did, like I used to ♪
♪ And oh… ♪
Well, look who showed up.
Here's your wristband.
Well, have a good time.
Oh, you… Uh, you weren't…
Actually, I have to…
go take care of a few things.
-[laughs]
-[Juliet] You two go ahead.
[Teagan] Okay. Huh.
Okay, come on. Let's get a drink.
["No Broke Boys"
by Disco Lines and Tinashe playing]
♪ Ain't no lie, ain't no shade
Shame on me, then you know he paid ♪
♪ Look so good, makes no sense
Badass bitch with my badass friends ♪
♪ No broke boys, ain't no shade
…on me, then you know he paid ♪
♪ No broke boys, no new friends… ♪
-[Josh] Oh, really now?
-[Britney laughs]
You look so cute.
You didn't bring your boat?
It's out for maintenance
with my other boat.
Mm.
[boys laughing and clamoring]
[Teagan] This is so shady.
Welcome to Eagle's Cove.
Can't really use a fake ID
when everyone knows your name.
Isn't there practice tomorrow morning?
It's a dock party.
Cam, my main bear! Bro, how you doing?
And the boat rocker.
Bro, because of you, I got upgraded.
Uh, I didn't switch the seats.
-No, no. But you spoke truth to power.
-Don't think that's what that means.
Hey, hey, tequila.
You, me, Chamomile, make three.
Cheers, ladies.
-Cheers.
-Cheers. Ladies.
[giggling] Okay.
[Teagan] Ooh. [laughing]
Well, I guess the gloves are off.
Here I am being a gentleman,
trying not to get you drunk.
Wow, okay, let's make it interesting.
Get one in,
and you can drink or answer a question.
Okay.
-Turns out I'm a beer pong shark.
-[Teagan laughs]
I heard you row. Are you any good?
I was a Southwest junior champ.
I had my eyes set on Stanford.
Stanford?
One of their scouts gave me his card
at the regatta last year.
I was hoping for U-Dub.
Why Stanford?
My dad rowed for Stanford.
I thought I'd get him a Stanford cowbell
when I got in, but, uh…
Maybe one day
I'll make it back to California.
[ball clatters and bounces]
[Cam] Why'd you move?
My dad, he… uh…
passed away, and we needed a change.
Uh, what about you? Why U-Dub?
Why U-Dub?
They're a D1 crew.
I'd be on an Olympic track.
-And there's this engineering program.
-You wanna be an Olympian and an engineer?
Wow.
I'd be the first in my family
to go to college.
Don't tell anyone.
[dance music playing]
Tequila.
Crew shots, come on.
I'm not really
into tequila right now, actually.
Fair.
But, like… Oh don't be sore.
The boat was faster with me.
Fair and square.
It's fine.
You're mad at me.
You're seriously mad at me. Okay.
There's only one way to end this.
-Bear hug! Come here, man.
-Okay.
-You love this. You love me. Baloo.
-No. Dude!
-Baloo. Yeah.
-Okay, Bronson.
-Bye.
-I didn't do it. Okay.
Lighten up.
Just a little.
Hey. Are you okay?
Sorry. You know my brother
likes to rile you up like that. It's…
Okay. Okay, okay. Take it easy.
-Leave some for the rest of us.
-Can you not? That's controlling.
What, are you mad at me?
No. There's a lot going on, and…
That new girl
is making me look like an asshole.
-And--
-You're thinking about the new girl?
-No, I'm not.
-Why are you thinking about the--
I just need some space.
Okay.
Something's up with him.
No disrespect,
but Josh can be a moody bitch.
Hey, he's still my guy. Love and support.
Love and support.
We were fine,
but ever since he got back
from training camp in Baltimore,
he's just been acting weird.
[Amber] Do you think something went down?
I don't know.
He silenced a call from a 410 number
when he thought I wasn't looking.
That's a Baltimore area code.
-[Amber] Uh…
-I know.
Oh, what is she doing here?
Oh, my God, do you know about her?
No.
I did a little cyberstalking.
I found something
you might be interested in.
-Thanks for hanging with me.
-[mic feedback squeals]
[Britney] Hello. Hi.
Hi, everyone. Oh, hi!
[sighs] I just wanted to say
that you should watch your bags, people.
This is a public service announcement.
We have a thief in our midst.
[people murmuring]
[reporter] …when it was discovered
that luxury hotelier, David Tao,
had allegedly defrauded investors
out of nearly $47 million.
Tao, who built the White Aspen chain
of boutique hotels across California,
is accused of misappropriating funds
to maintain
the property's lavish operations
and his family's lifestyle.
Oh!
-Authorities have seized assets…
-I know.
…including their home and vehicles.
Tao remains at large,
with federal warrants
issued for their arrest.
The FBI is asking
anyone with information about…
Where's your dad, Teagan?
Where's the money? Care to comment?
-All right, Britney.
-Oh.
[tense music playing]
-Is that you?
-Uh…
-You said your dad was dead.
-[exhales]
Did he really steal all that money?
I, um…
You should go.
Okay.
[murmuring]
[laughs quietly]
[sad laugh]
What happened to you?
I have finally figured out
how to convince my mom to come visit.
What happened to you?
[laughs wryly] Just a public execution.
I don't really wanna
talk about it right now.
Well, you can tell me
when I'm back at school.
Wait, you're not… going tomorrow?
No, I've got to get my car fixed.
What? What's wrong with your car?
[gasps]
-Wha…
-[dramatic music playing]
Oh, my God. What are you doing?
-You should probably get going.
-What?
Mom, please come and get me.
-[Teagan] Oh!
-Oh, my God.
[Ella clears throat]
[Teagan groans]
-Come on, you.
-[Teagan moans]
Hey, it's okay. [laughs]
[Ella groans]
-[Teagan] Yeah. Ooh…
-Oh!
[Teagan] Oh, my God.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I…
may have messed up.
Just a little bit.
-You did.
-I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
What?
At least you're talking to me.
Oh, okay, like you want to talk.
Of course I do.
[laughs]
You can't even admit
that Dad wrecked our lives.
Hey, that's not true. Come on.
See? You just…
You can't talk about anything real.
And I found his duffel bag.
I saw that you hid it from me.
I just want to know,
like, what do you know?
Stop sugarcoating everything
and just tell me the truth.
Truth?
[emotional music playing]
The truth is that I hate Eagle's Cove.
Twenty years ago, I left here,
I promised I would never be back,
and here I am.
Because your dad just left.
[exhaled]
I'm not upset.
I'm furious.
But you know what?
As mad as I get,
I remember he's your father.
I still can't believe
he would do this to us.
But he did.
I kept his bag.
I don't know why.
I think I thought
maybe there'd be some answers.
And there weren't.
Now I don't know
whether I should hold onto it or burn it.
[laughs]
No. Don't.
Don't burn it.
I'm so angry.
[Ella] I know.
At him, Mom,
but I really miss him. [crying]
Oh, God, me too.
[Ella sighs]
-Asshole.
-[Teagan laughs]
[both laughing]
[scrubbing]
It's 15 past, where is everyone?
Freaking dock party.
You sure you don't wanna
scrap the boys team
and try and round up some girls instead?
[laughs] That's a nice try.
Easton's never gonna make
a big push for a girls' team
until the boys start winning.
-Hey, go give me a quick lap.
-Just… Yeah, one second.
You are the coxswain of this team.
-You're supposed to lead it.
-I said give me a minute.
No wonder you're losing.
Excuse me?
You're here hungover
instead of practicing.
Do you know how many people
would kill to get in that boat? I would.
That's cute, but the men are rowing.
Enjoy sweeping.
Huh. Maybe you're onto something.
You want in the boat?
Position's up for grabs. Coxswain.
Liam, Teagan.
You're both going to race for that spot.
Uh, sorry, what?
Okay. Two boats, four rowers, one K.
Liam and Teagan, you each coxswain a boat.
[laughs] I'm not racing her.
Then you're not coxswain.
Losing team
has to clean the docks for a month.
-What?
-Pick your teams. Teagan, you're up.
-Me?
-Come on.
-Cam, Baloo, Josh.
-That's cute, but I'm not rowing for her.
She called your name.
She can take Ryder.
She can have Crabcatcher
and I'll take Noah.
-Fine.
-[Hayden] All right, let's go.
These guys are never going to row for me.
Listen, you're not like
any coxie they had before.
You can pick up on things that they don't.
I don't know how to cox. I'm a rower.
All right, so you know exactly
what it's like to be in their shoes.
Use it. Empathize with them.
Get in their heads.
Listen, this is your chance
to get in the boat.
Do you want it?
Yeah, I do.
Then prove it.
Yeah, okay.
-[indistinct dialog]
-[Teagan clears throat]
I know you don't want to be
on my team, but…
I'm the thing standing in between you
and a month's worth of goose shit. So…
Here's the plan.
The first 250,
we'll let them set the pace.
Liam won't bring them out quick.
He has too much to prove.
When they lag, we'll make our move.
Okay.
[Teagan] Great.
Uh, wait.
I know you only joined to throw the race.
-What, who, me?
-Yeah.
Consider this.
You're only ever gonna be Josh's sidekick.
Piss off.
He'll never consider you as an equal
until you beat him.
["The Best" by Tina Turner playing]
All right. In your ready positions.
We got this.
All right, boys. Let's get this.
Let's show this chick what's up at Easton.
-[horn blows]
-Three-quarter!
[Teagan] Row!
Row. Okay, push. Or legs.
Get off the rate in two. That's one.
That's two. Here we go.
Give it to me, Josh.
Let's go.
And row!
And swing.
And legs. Keep with our plan. Let's go.
Come on. You got this.
And okay, here it is. They're losing it.
Let's take it to them. Come on.
Okay?
Come on. Come on, Ryder.
♪ And it can't be wrong ♪
Okay. You really going to let him win?
♪ Take my heart and make it strong, babe ♪
That's right, Ryder. Let's go. Push!
And legs! Let's go, let's go!
♪ Better than anyone ♪
[Liam] Hey! They're catching up.
We gotta go, we gotta go!
[Teagan] That's right, Ryder.
You got this. Come on!
-And row! Try to bring up pace!
-[Liam] All together! Come on.
They're right on us. Let's go!
Go, go, let's go!
[Teagan] Come on. Five more!
We're losing to a girl!
Can you go a little harder!
And three. Almost there. Two… one!
[horn blows]
Let's go!
Let's go! You guys did it!
You just won! We just won.
Let's go! Teagan! Not bad, crew girl.
Are you freaking kidding me?
Nice job, Ryder.
[exhales]
[Baloo] Hey!
Make my baby spotless.
You guys are goddamn losers.
Just wait.
You'll come crawling back to me.
You know what?
I'm out of here. Who's with me?
Sick.
Hey. Uh…
I just wanted to say sorry for…
lying to you. I'm kind of a mess.
I get it. I also need to focus on crew.
Everything else is a distraction.
Teagan.
You made the team.
So access to the ergs, rowing tanks,
boats. Keep up your training.
What about access to the water
for sculling?
-Or… competing at the regattas?
-Yeah.
Get the boys winning again
and we'll see how far we can push admin.
But remember, eights is a team sport.
The team comes first. Are you ready?
I'm ready. Yeah. [laughing]
All right, boys.
Meet your new coxie, Teagan Tao.
[Baloo] Whoo! Teagan Tao!
Let's go, girl! Up top.
Down below. Split the difference.
Double time.
-Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Ah!
-Ow.
Whoo!
What's good?
[Teagan laughs awkwardly]
[stirring music playing]
[Baloo] Mm-hmm.
[Teagan laughs]
[Teagan] A good catch
can send you soaring.
Mom? Guess what? Hello?
That's boring.
Boring.
[tense music playing]
But one bad catch can end your run.
[intriguing electronic
dance music playing]
[music ends]